if you're trying to increase your intake
of omega-3 fatty acids we don't blame
you it's one of the most popular
wellness supplements on the market the
industry is currently valued at an
astounding 30 billion dollars it's often
used as a natural remedy that could
potentially reduce inflammation fish oil
is so popular that countless brands have
done their own takes on the product some
value sustainability others
affordability others just don't want
something that contains pork we've
explored dozens of the best fish shows
on the market so you can find the right
one for your needs today we're talking
about the best fish oil the best fish
oil for athletes the best krill oil and
a lot more if you want to see the full
written version of this video so you can
scroll around at your own pace and also
check out all our scientific references
make sure you just google that with
barbin plus best fish oil oh and before
i forget if you want to buy into these
products or check them out on their
official website they've got links to
every single one of them in the
description below you can click on right
there first up is the best official
overall this supplement is sustainably
sourced provides transparency in its
sourcing and it doesn't come back up
fishy most importantly packs a serious
punch of amiga 3s we're talking about
legions triton fish oil each serving
contains 4 grams of fish oil 1.44 grams
of epa and 960 milligrams of dha fats as
well as vitamin e and lemon oil to
prevent oxidation rancidity and fish oil
burps that some people want to avoid it
sustainably saw some peruvian anchovies
and sardines from fisheries that have
been approved by friend of the sea which
is a project of the world sustainability
organization that verifies sustainable
practices and it also meets the
stringent purity standards of the
european pharmacopoeia reference
standards council for responsible
nutrition and global organization for
epa and dha omega-3 this facial has also
been molecularly distilled to reduce
toxins and chemicals it's worth noting
that each dose is for soft gels though
which may be a lot for some people
next up is the best krill oil acrylic
oil supplements not technically fish
right it comes from krill we threw it in
here anyway they're loaded with omega-3s
and they're thought to be more easily
absorbed and also they tend to have a
lot of antioxidants as well right the
transparent labs krill oil here it comes
from antarctic krill contains no mercury
includes omega-3 fatty acids so it's 120
milligrams of epa's 55 milligrams of
dhas and it's made to be easier on the
stomach when compared to most fish oils
due to acrylic oil is easier to digest
phospholipid form next up is the best
fish oil for athletes for this one i'm
definitely gonna go with legion's fish
oil called triton i recommend this for
athletes who want a pretty high dose
official to potentially help reduce
inflammation a big concern for a lot of
athletes anyone who's concerned with
sustainability as well because again
these fisheries are approved by friend
of the sea uh people who prefer a
product that has been molecularly
distilled to reduce toxins and
impurities and chemicals that kind of
thing of the fish oils out there this is
one of the priciest
largely because i imagine it's certified
by so many different sustainability
organizations but that's the big pro for
most people next up is the best
supplement stack with fish oil for many
people fish oil is not the only
supplement in their regimen if you're an
athlete looking to buy all your
supplements including one with omega-3
fatty acids in one go this pick is for
you we're talking about transparent labs
muscle building essentials stack this
supplement that contains transparent
labs pre-series bulk which is a
pre-workout supplement that may help
athletes to build muscle and work out
more effectively you also get the
protein series grass-fed whey protein
isolate this is 88 protein by weight one
of the industry's highest along with
transparent labs strength series crea
pure hmb which is a creatine monohydrate
that may help to increase strength and
power output and muscle size and lastly
it contains
krill oil which contains long chain
omega-3 fatty acids epas and dhas
phospholipids and astaxanthin the
antioxidant it may also potentially be
easier to digest than fish oil and it
does not have 50 burps either next up is
the best fish oil pill and we have this
category here because there are plenty
of fish oil supplements out there that
are just a straight liquid that you put
on a teaspoon we get into that one a
little bit later on but the best pills
out there that's going to be legion's
triton fish oil so i would recommend
this to people who want a fish oil they
can consume in pill form for convenience
it's easy to travel with and everything
else people who want a high dose of fish
oil as well because it has 4 000
milligrams of it in this product and
also anyone who wants fish oil pills
that are not made with pork because
there are a lot of pills up there where
the encasing is made from pork gelatin
and that makes it off-limits for a lot
of people for a variety of reasons uh
these ones do not contain pork next up
is the best amiga 3 fish oil all fish
oils contain omega-3 fatty acids but
some contain more than others so this
pick has a particularly high dose of
omega-3s it is legion's triton fish oil
you get four grams of fish oil it has
2.4 grams of fatty acids in here omega-3
fatty acids it's much higher than many
officials on the market the epa fatty
acids can potentially decrease
inflammation whereas the dha ones could
potentially help with brain function
according to some research well you can
get these omega-3 fatty acids from some
food like seafood and algae a facial
supplement is an easy way to increase
your intake legion's fish oil here is
essentially sourced in peruvian
anchovies and sardines it also contains
vitamin e and lemon oil so next up the
best liquid fish oil while the most
common foil of fish oil supplements is
pills liquid fish oil is also an option
that may appeal to consumers as well it
helps you to control your dosage a bit
more accurately based on like what
you've eaten that day or whatever and
also it may absorb more quickly upon
consumption so liquid fish oil is the go
for a lot of people our favorite is
nordic naturals omega omega-3 since
nordic naturals omega-3 comes in liquid
your body does not need to digest the
capsule once you get the fish oil in
other words you're able to absorb it
more correctly on top of that the
products omega-3 fish oils come in the
triglyceride molecular form which is a
form naturally found in fish which could
help with absorption as well next up is
the best fish oil for women this product
gets its omega-3 straight from the same
source as fish algae so we're talking
about performance labs omega-3 here
while omega-3s are good for both men and
women women may benefit for different
reasons or for extra reasons for example
the petrol anti-inflammatory properties
of omega-3s could reduce inflammation
during menstrual cramps or for those who
battle with rheumatoid arthritis which
is more common in women as is
osteoporosis omega-3 here from
performance lab contains 1 100
milligrams of omega-3 fatty acids which
includes 600 milligrams of epa 300 grams
of dha and also performance labs sources
that omega-3s from algae is very
interesting and also means these are
vegan which is a very very rare thing
next up is the best cheap fish oil if
you're on a budget but you still want to
incorporate high quality fish oil
supplement into your supplement regimen
uh this pick is one of the least
expensive fish oils you'll find
especially if you buy a lot of it it's
bulk supplements bulk supplements fish
oil uh packs 1 000 milligrams of fish
oil into one soft gel which also
includes 300 milligrams of combined epa
and dha fats you can take one soft gel
up to three times daily to increase your
intake while this product is third party
tested there isn't a lot of information
listed about the sustainability
practices so if that's something you
prioritize there's going to be a pick
for you if that's something you
prioritize you probably shouldn't also
looking for the cheapest fish oil you
can possibly get you may get fishy burps
as well but the price certainly is right
with bulk supplements you can get them
in bulk so you can get them in 100 soft
gel packs up to 6 000 soft gel packs so
you don't have to think about
replenishing your stock for like literal
years although you know check the
expiration date to make sure that's a
possibility next up is the best
sustainably sourced fish oil if you're
environmentally conscious you want to
pick a supplement that meets rigorous
testing standards and sources this oil
from fish that aren't endangered
sports researchers omega-3 fish oil
triple strength omega-3 fish oil has
certifications from the international
fish oil standards the marine
stewardship council and nsf
international the supplement is also
tested to ensure there are no gmos
genetically modified organisms each
single soft gel serving provides 250
milligrams of wild alaskan pollock fish
oil concentrate which includes 690
milligrams of epas and 260 milligrams of
bhas the facial is extracted from
pollock trimmings immediately after a
catch to better ensure freshness and
that freshness and all those
certifications does bump up the price
tag next up is the best fish oil that
you can buy in bulk replenishing your
fish oil supplement every month can get
pretty tiring for some folks for those
who want to buy a lot of fish oil soft
gels in one go this is a really solid
pick for you xbox supplements because
they do bulk supplements they are known
for their bulk supplements they're bulk
buy products and their fish oil is no
different you can buy this fish gel in
bags 100
300 even 6 000 soft gels you can take
one soft gel three times a day is what
they recommend so like that six thousand
soft gel bag you know could get you like
five years or something you know double
check the expiration date but still you
can even subscribe to further save on
having to buy them by having to put time
into buying more and more fish oil so
it's pretty impressive in that regard
it's really good people who don't love
thinking about making sure that their
supplements arrive on time all the time
over and over and over again all right
that about does it for our best fish
oils video let us know below which your
favorite facial supplement is and again
if you want to see the full written
version of this article so you can go
through it at your own pace just google
barban plus best fish oil
[Music]
you